<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on Girish Luckhun</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on Girish Luckhun</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:12:04 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m thinking of ending things</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/05/im-thinking-of-ending-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 19:16:11 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/05/im-thinking-of-ending-things/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I’m thinking of ending things. Once this thought arrives, it stays. It sticks. It lingers. It dominates. There’s not much I can do about it. Trust me. It doesn’t go away. It’s there whether I like it or not. It’s there when I eat. When I go to bed. It’s there when I sleep. It’s there when I wake up. It’s always there. Always.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-― Iain Reid, I&amp;rsquo;m Thinking of Ending Things&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A few months have passed since I was thinking about why I can&#39;t write a blog.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/a-few-months-have-passed-since-i-was-thinking-about-why-i-cant-write-a-blog./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 20:34:16 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/a-few-months-have-passed-since-i-was-thinking-about-why-i-cant-write-a-blog./</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I think there&amp;rsquo;s a point in blogging just because you can record your feelings and what you&amp;rsquo;re doing even if you don&amp;rsquo;t show it to anyone, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to come up with something to write about. There were days when I didn&amp;rsquo;t think to blog about it, couldn&amp;rsquo;t make any progress, or rather, didn&amp;rsquo;t pick up the pen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There must be a reason for this, I understand. Well, the &lt;code&gt;blogging experience&lt;/code&gt; is not good, and I have been thinking about it for several months, thinking that I need to change the system and how to change it. had passed. It&amp;rsquo;s hilarious.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023 - Malyasia Trip</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/11/2023-malyasia-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 01:48:45 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/11/2023-malyasia-trip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Okay, it&amp;rsquo;s been some time since I wrote last and I thought to write about my vacation in Malaysia. The planning has been going on for days after one of my friends got married back in July; A tug of Excitement. Finally, on the scheduled day(07 Aug) we boarded the Mauritius Airlines flight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./images/01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;day-1---arrival&#34;&gt;Day 1 - Arrival&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We arrived the following day around 3 PM. It was so freaking hot, fortunately every building, cars, bus had aircon. We stayed at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.booking.com/hotel/my/msp.en-gb.html&#34;&gt;cheapest hotel&lt;/a&gt; we could find on booking.com in Kuala Lumpur. Although, we did not like the small bathroom and toilet, the staff was nice and they cleaned our room every 3 days giving up new towel, shampoo pillow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember you are Human too.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/remember-you-are-human-too./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 22:23:42 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/remember-you-are-human-too./</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of us know the saying, &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sticks and stones may break my bones, but words will never hurt me.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; However, this statement may not hold true for those of us who have experienced hurtful name-calling. If you have been called names or seen someone who has, you know how damaging these words can be. When it comes to name calling, many teens or children may not understand that name calling is also a form of bullying. They might start out by joking, but calling someone a name with the intent of hurting them is not okay.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Be a Loner Without Being Lonely?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/can-you-be-a-loner-without-being-lonely/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:00:27 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/can-you-be-a-loner-without-being-lonely/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./images/01.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;image01&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;friendship-and-solitude&#34;&gt;Friendship and solitude&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Amidst a period characterized by a pandemic, financial downturn, remote work and social distancing, relationships have been tested.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is widely believed that a rise in divorce rates is imminent. This is not surprising, as financial difficulties can put a strain on a marriage, and also couples these days have to spend more time… with each other. Today, however, I would like to focus on our wider social circles and friendships. More precisely, I want to reflect on the potential advantages of being a loner.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realizing Nobody Has Ever Had a Crush on You</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/realizing-nobody-has-ever-had-a-crush-on-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 15:11:19 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/realizing-nobody-has-ever-had-a-crush-on-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Realizing that nobody has ever had a crush on you can be a devastating realization. It can leave you feeling unlovable, unwanted, and alone. The weight of this realization can feel suffocating and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to fall into a spiral of negative thoughts and self-doubt.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You may begin to wonder what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with you, why you haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to attract any romantic attention. You may start to compare yourself to others and feel like you don&amp;rsquo;t measure up. You may feel like you&amp;rsquo;re doomed to a life of loneliness and isolation. The reality is that attraction is complicated and often out of our control. It&amp;rsquo;s not a reflection of your worth as a person, but it can be hard to remember that in the face of this realization, you may start to feel like you&amp;rsquo;re not good enough, like you&amp;rsquo;ll never find someone who loves you for who you are.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My current approach to social media </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/my-current-approach-to-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 19:17:31 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/my-current-approach-to-social-media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been doing a lot of thinking about my relationship with social media. Over the years, I’ve struggled between enjoying it’s benefits while also watching it consume valuable time that I will never get back. I would take social media breaks, in the hopes that I would be able to have more control over my time while still being active on the platforms. The problem was that I kept coming back and getting sucked into the same cycle of consumption over creation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the most important choice in life?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/what-is-the-most-important-choice-in-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 19:16:11 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/what-is-the-most-important-choice-in-life/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The most important choice in life is not to choose what kind of work to do, nor to choose which company to invest in, but to choose who to marry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first time I heard this statement came from Bill Gates and Buffett. Of course, the two of them are good friends and and the possibility of mutual influence cannot be ruled out，but I believe this is a common choice for all wise men. They all believe that the most important thing in life is not which company to invest in, but who to marry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My experience so far</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022/12/my-experience-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 19:12:22 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022/12/my-experience-so-far/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now that 2022 is almost over, I decided to write about my experience so far in general.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;university-life&#34;&gt;University life&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Electrical with computer Science, yes, was an actual course at UOM(university of Mauritius) that I took during my time there. I really didn’t enjoy my university life as much as I should have. I felt like during my entire 20s I was just trailing along, not really enjoying life, always resentful and regretful of my choices, and just wasting my time altogether. But I made some really good friends along the way. The only thing I&amp;rsquo;m really proud of achieving is getting an A+ on my dissertation. It would not have been possible without the help of my friend. We literally stayed up all night just to finish it. The project was an Android app that can be used to detect any infringement on the road while you&amp;rsquo;re driving. Feel free to contact me if you want more info; in any case, here&amp;rsquo;s my [research paper] (&lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-030-90618-4_18)&#34;&gt;https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-030-90618-4_18)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So I went to my first Night Club</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022/11/so-i-went-to-my-first-night-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 19:11:02 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2022/11/so-i-went-to-my-first-night-club/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An introvert… clubbing. Something about that sentence almost seems paradoxical.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So 26 and I have yet to go to a &amp;ldquo;dance club&amp;rdquo; and for the most part, I am really unbothered by that. Nightclubs are challenging territories for a lot of introverts. Nearly every aspect of the environment puts us outside of our ideal comfort zone. That’s not to say that we can’t still enjoy them. It just requires a little bit more effort to get us there and into the right mindset to enjoy it. It is usually not my cup of tea, but my friends asked me if I wanted to go dancing to &lt;a href=&#34;https://lakaz.mu/&#34;&gt;Lakaz&lt;/a&gt; and as an introvert I am, I more than happily accepted the invitation. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why I did because 1) I had to work that day 2) my anxiety when i see a lot of people 3) I usually talked myself out of going because I didn’t think I’d have a good time. I’d been trying to work the nerve to go out to one lately though because I wanted to break out of my comfort zone. I figured if tonight went well, I’d push further past my boundaries next time and approach some girls the next time I go. (Just kidding xD) I&amp;rsquo;m thinking it was sure curiosity, so nonetheless I pressed on to the night life on the country side of country.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
