<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NightClub on Girish Luckhun</title>
    <link>https://girishluckhun.com/tags/nightclub/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NightClub on Girish Luckhun</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 19:31:56 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://girishluckhun.com/tags/nightclub/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>So I went to my first Night Club</title>
      <link>https://girishluckhun.com/posts/2022/11/so-i-went-to-my-first-night-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 19:11:02 +0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://girishluckhun.com/posts/2022/11/so-i-went-to-my-first-night-club/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An introvert… clubbing. Something about that sentence almost seems paradoxical.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So 26 and I have yet to go to a &amp;ldquo;dance club&amp;rdquo; and for the most part, I am really unbothered by that. Nightclubs are challenging territories for a lot of introverts. Nearly every aspect of the environment puts us outside of our ideal comfort zone. That’s not to say that we can’t still enjoy them. It just requires a little bit more effort to get us there and into the right mindset to enjoy it. It is usually not my cup of tea, but my friends asked me if I wanted to go dancing to &lt;a href=&#34;https://lakaz.mu/&#34;&gt;Lakaz&lt;/a&gt; and as an introvert I am, I more than happily accepted the invitation. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why I did because 1) I had to work that day 2) my anxiety when i see a lot of people 3) I usually talked myself out of going because I didn’t think I’d have a good time. I’d been trying to work the nerve to go out to one lately though because I wanted to break out of my comfort zone. I figured if tonight went well, I’d push further past my boundaries next time and approach some girls the next time I go. (Just kidding xD) I&amp;rsquo;m thinking it was sure curiosity, so nonetheless I pressed on to the night life on the country side of country.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
